eqservers.com 2019-03-15

# EqServers LLC's Privacy Policy

**BY SIGNING UP FOR AN Eqservers LLC (THE “COMPANY”) ACCOUNT AND/OR USING ITS PRODUCTS, SERVICES, WEBSITES AND MOBILE APPLICATIONS, YOU ARE AGREEING TO BE BOUND BY THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND ALL TERMS AND CONDITIONS INCORPORATED BY REFERENCE IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY. ANY USER’S USE OR CONTINUED USE OF THE COMPANY’S PRODUCTS, SERVICES, WEBSITES OR MOBILE APPLICATIONS CONSTITUTES ACCEPTANCE OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.**

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please feel free to contact us by e-mail, at Privacy [at] eqservers.com

In connection with serving content and providing analytics and advertising services, third parties may collect certain information about your visits to this and other websites and we may receive information regarding the use of the Site and the effectiveness of our advertisements. These advertising networks, advertisers, advertising agencies, analytics service providers, and other vendors may set and access their own tracking technologies (including cookies and web beacons) and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you and your online browsing activities.

The Site is operated in the United States. If you are located outside the United States and use the Site or provide us with any information, you consent to the transfer, processing, and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be as comprehensive as those in the country where you reside or are a citizen.

### Information You Provide to the Site

Eqservers may ask you to provide “Personal Information” (information that identifies you as a specific individual, such as, but not limited to, your name or e-mail address and other contact information), and information necessary to facilitate financial transactions between Eqservers and you (such as, but not limited to, financial account numbers). We may also collect demographic information (such as, but not limited to, your age, occupation, postal code, or similar information), certain information about your preferences and interests, customer questions and support information, and other information collected through surveys, chat features, and polls made available on the Site. If we combine these types of other information about you with Personal Information, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy. 

The Site is a general audience web site. The Site does not knowingly collect any Personal Information from children younger than the age of thirteen (13), If we become aware that personal information from a child under the age of 13 has been collected, we will use all reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

### Information Third Parties Provide About You

We may also receive information about you from third parties. For example, if you are on another website that provides information about hosting service providers like Eqservers and you request to receive information from Eqservers, that website will forward your contact and other information to us so that we may contact you as requested. Third parties may also provide information about you in connection with a marketing arrangement we may have with those third parties. 

We also may supplement the information we collect with outside records from third parties in order to provide you with the information, goods, or services you have requested to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We may combine the information we receive from those other outside sources with information we collect through the Site. In those cases, we will apply this Privacy Policy to the combined information.

### Cookies and Tracking and Similar Technologies

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to the Site, we and our third-party service providers, including any third-party content, advertising, and analytics providers, may use a variety of technologies that automatically or passively collect certain information about your use of the Site whenever you visit or interact with the Site (“Site Usage Information”). Site Usage Information may include the browser and operating system you are using, the URL or advertisement that referred you to our Site, the search terms you entered into a search engine that led you to our Site (if applicable), actions you take on the Site and all of the areas within our Site that you visit, and the time of day you visited the Site, among other information. Site Usage Information may also include the unique IP address or other unique identifiers (“Device Identifier”) for any computer, mobile phone, or other device (any, a “Device”) used to access the Site. A Device Identifier is a unique value that is automatically assigned to your Device, so that our servers can identify your Device by its Device Identifier. 

We may use Site Usage Information for a variety of purposes, including enhancing or otherwise improving the Site and our products and services. We may associate Site Usage Information with you as a specific and identifiable person. When we do so, we treat the combined information as Personal Information.

### How we collect information:

**Cookies.** We use the information provided by the cookies to change the way our website looks to you; to keep you logged in to certain areas of the website; and to collect demographic data about where visitors to our website go and how they behave. We do not use this data to identify Users individually. Cookie information may be shared with, and used by, our Partners in the following circumstances: to enable them to assist us in marketing and providing our services.. 

**Customer Inquiries** If you contact us about a problem or with a question we may ask you for specific information related to the reason you have contacted us (Customer Inquiry Information). This information may be tied or input into your Registration and Billing Information. 

**Embedded Scripts.** An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, such as the specific links you click on, where your mouse moves, what advertising you clicked to direct you to the Site, and other information that is relevant. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our server or a third-party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter. Embedded Scripts may collect information that you enter into forms on our website, which may be used by Eqservers for purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy. 

**Social Media.** Our website includes social media features (such as the Facebook "Like" button). These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our website, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets may be hosted by a third party or directly on our website. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the feature. 

In addition, we may use a variety of other technologies that collect similar information for security and fraud detection purposes

Eqservers may share non-personally identifiable information, such as aggregated user statistics, with third parties in our discretion. We do not share your Personal Information with third parties for those third parties’ marketing purposes unless we first provide you with the opportunity to opt-in or opt-out of such sharing. We may share the information we have collected about you, including Personal Information, as disclosed at the time you provide your information, with your consent, as described in this Privacy Policy, and in the following circumstances:

Eqservers may use information collected through the Site, including Personal Information and Site Usage Information, to: (1) allow you to use the Site and to provide related service, including responding to your questions and comments; (2) fulfill transactions and process your registration, orders and payments, including verifying the information you provide is accurate and active; (3) administer and develop our business relationship with you and the company you represent; (4) tailor content, recommendations and offers we display to you on the Site and elsewhere online; (5) provide you with information, products or services that you have requested or agreed to receive or that we otherwise believe will interest you, including, information and special offers from us, our advertisers, and our third party business partners; (6) conduct internal analyses, such as surveys and market research; (7) improve the Site, our products and services and for internal business purposes; (8) assess your employment application for a position with Eqservers and prepare related governmental and internal statistics reports; (9) contact you with administrative communications and, in our discretion, changes to Site policies; and (10) for purposes disclosed at the time you provide your information and as further described or permitted in this Privacy Policy; (11) to remember and restore your preferences when you return to the website; or (12) otherwise with your consent.

### When You Agree to Receive Information from Third Parties or Request That We Share Your Information.

You may be presented with an opportunity to receive information and/or marketing offers from one or more third parties. If you agree at that time to have your Personal Information shared, your Personal Information will be disclosed to that third party (or parties) and will be subject to the privacy policy and practices of that third party. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of third parties. If you later decide that you no longer want to receive communications from a third party, you will need to contact that third party directly. You also may request, sometimes through your use of an interactive feature or third-party application, that we share information about you with a third party and we will typically do so under those circumstances.

### Third Parties Providing Services on our Behalf.

We may share information with third parties so that they may provide services to you, Eqservers, and the Site. Examples include conducting website usage analysis, sending e-mail or other communications on our behalf, providing sales and marketing assistance, or performing other administrative or support services. When we do so, the information is only to be used to provide services or help us provide services. Third-party systems used to deliver services to you may retain your information for a period of time after the services are provided.

### Promotions

We may offer sweepstakes, contests, and other promotions (any, a “Promotion”) that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the official rules that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, except where prohibited by law, allowing the sponsor(s) of the Promotion to use your name, voice, likeness, or other indicia of persona in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If you choose to enter a Promotion, your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion’s official rules, such as on a winners list.

### Legal Reasons

We may access, preserve and share information about customers with companies, organizations, governmental entities or individuals outside of Eqservers if we believe, in good faith, that the law requires us to do so. This may include, but is not limited to, responding to subpoenas, court orders or other legal processes (such as law enforcement requests). We may also access, preserve and share information about customers as necessary to: (i) establish or exercise Eqservers’s legal rights or defend against any legal claim including threatened claims involving Eqservers based on the anonymity of a domain name; (ii) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected fraud or other illegal activities; (iii) prevent death or serious physical harm to any person; or (iv) investigate violations of Eqservers’s Terms of Service..

### Business Transfers

Eqservers may share information, including Personal Information, with its parent, subsidiaries, and affiliates, primarily for business and operational purposes. Eqservers may also disclose and transfer your information, including Personal Information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Site or applicable database; or (ii) if Eqservers (or any of its affiliated, parent, or subsidiary companies) assigns its rights regarding any of your information to a third party; or (iii) in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of certain of our ownership interests, assets, or both, or other corporate change, including, without limitation, during the course of any due diligence process.

The Site may contain content served by third parties and we work with vendors (including network advertisers, ad agencies, and analytics companies) to provide us with information regarding traffic on the Site, to serve advertisements, including our advertisements elsewhere online, and to provide us with information regarding the use of the Site and the effectiveness of our advertisements. For example, if you clicked on one of our advertisements that led you to the Site, our service provider(s) may be able to tell us information about your interaction, such as, but not limited to: which advertisement you clicked on, where you were viewing the advertisement, how often you viewed or clicked on it, and so forth. In connection with serving content and providing analytics and advertisement services, third parties may collect certain information about your visits to the Site or other websites. Some of these parties may collect Personal Information when you visit the Site or other websites or services. These third parties may set and access their own tracking technologies (including cookies and web beacons) and may otherwise collect or have access to your Device Identifier, Site Usage Information, and related information about you. Cookies and web beacons, including those set by third-party network advertisers, may be used to, among other things, target advertisements, prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times, and to conduct research regarding the usefulness of certain advertisements to you. We may share Device Identifier and Site Usage Information about visitors with third-party advertising companies, analytics providers, and other vendors for similar purposes.

Correcting/Updating Personal Information. If a customer's information changes, or if a customer no longer desires our services, we will endeavor to provide a way to correct, update or remove that customer's personal data in our records. In most cases, this can be achieved via our billing system at https://www.eqservers.com/eqpanel/clientarea.php or by emailing us at privacy [at] eqservers.com. 

**Opt Out.** By default, customers will receive invoices, any system updates, Eqservers newsletters and other mailings. Customers are able to opt out of newsletters and mailings by using the unsubscribe link in any promotional email or as otherwise provided in the communication. Please note that customers may not opt out of receiving important system notifications or emails about their accounts. 

**Public Forums.** Please remember that any information you may disclose or post on public areas of our websites or the Internet, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas. To request removal of your personal information from our community forums or testimonials, contact us at privacy [at] eqservers.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know why we are unable to do so.

Eqservers takes commercially reasonable steps to protect your Personal Information. However, no data transmission over the Internet, wireless transmission, or electronic storage of information can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Please note that we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information we collect. You use our Site and provide us with your information at your own risk. Our employees are required to keep information covered by this Privacy Policy confidential – unless disclosure is authorized in this Privacy Policy, or by you.

The Site is operated in the United States. If you are located in the European Union, Canada, or elsewhere outside of the United States, please be aware that any information you provide to us may be transferred to and processed in the United States. By using the Site, or providing us with any information, you consent to this transfer, processing and storage of your information in the United States, a jurisdiction in which the privacy laws may not be different than those in the country where you reside or are a citizen.

We reserve the right to revise, amend, or modify this Privacy Policy at any time and in any manner. However, if we plan to materially change how we plan to use previously collected personal information, we will provide you with advance notice prior to the change becoming effective and an opportunity to opt-out of such differing uses. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practice
